<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Nymph Keepers on Elise Volkman</title>
    <link>https://elisevolkman.com/tags/the-nymph-keepers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Nymph Keepers on Elise Volkman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 08:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://elisevolkman.com/tags/the-nymph-keepers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Next?</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/what-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/what-next/</guid>
      <description>The Nymph Keepers is over.
Does that ever feel good to say! But I think it&amp;rsquo;s also a challenge, to move on from a project that big and fill that space with something new. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong; I haven&amp;rsquo;t stopped writing other drafts and working other stories, so there&amp;rsquo;s no shortage of projects. But this is a bit of a goodbye — a transition from one season into another, or from one focus toward something new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Out How the Story Ends</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/queen-of-the-nymphs-launch-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 07:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/queen-of-the-nymphs-launch-day/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Launch Day Maybe you have no trouble believing this, but I&amp;rsquo;m still in a bit of a daze: Queen of the Nymphs is here! Today is the day and Book III of the Nymph Keepers is ready and waiting for you. You can find out how the story ends wherever ebooks are sold.
But wait!
I Made You a Treat Because I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough to do, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d treat you to something a little extra special: Chapters 1 &amp;amp; 2 of Queen of the Nymphs, read by yours truly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart of the Forest, A Synopsis</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/heart-of-the-forest-synopsis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 12:15:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/heart-of-the-forest-synopsis/</guid>
      <description>SPOILERS FOR HEART OF THE FOREST AHEAD At the start of Heart of the Forest: Book II of the Nymph Keepers, the war between Ireece and Galia has just begun, sparked by the death of the ambassador — the Nymph Keeper — who Jay killed. Meanwhile, a new plot unravels in Fethens, threatening to unravel Forest’s life as court herbalist: Silic and Protis secretly poison the king of Ireece with Hellfire in a zealous attempt to put Terryn on the throne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roots of Blood, A Synopsis</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/roots-of-blood-synopsis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 12:06:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/roots-of-blood-synopsis/</guid>
      <description>SPOILERS FOR ROOTS OF BLOOD AHEAD After Jay saves Forest from the Butcher — the Nymph Keeper he had originally been working for in order to get the nymph blood he needed to help his sister — he takes her to his home city of Fethens. Forest expected this to be just another stop in a life of horrors. She tries to escape to the mountains, where she finds the rumoured mountain nymphs and hopes for refuge, but as a forest nymph, she cannot survive underground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queen of the Nymphs, Available for Pre-Order!</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/queen-of-the-nymphs-pre-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/queen-of-the-nymphs-pre-order/</guid>
      <description>Releasing August 12th… In the final book of The Nymph Keepers, Forest struggles with her duties as court herbalist and the expectations of a future queen as the rot ravaging Galia’s lands creeps over the borders into the other provinces.
And pre-orders are now OPEN.
That’s right. After weeks (months) of saying “soon,” I’m here to tell you that Queen of the Nymphs is HERE. And in the words of The Incredibles, “It’s bigger… [and] It’s better!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
