<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Work on Elise Volkman</title>
    <link>https://elisevolkman.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Work on Elise Volkman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 08:01:35 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://elisevolkman.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Tea Grannies Podcast</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/projects/the-tea-grannies-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 08:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/projects/the-tea-grannies-podcast/</guid>
      <description>Miraya Engelage and Elise Volkman bring you writing, editing, and reading tips from the tea-tables of their living rooms. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an experienced author or new writer, pour yourself a cup of tea and join them for discussions on first drafts, querying, and everything in between.
   Miraya and I met in 2018 when we both apparated into the Speculative Fiction cohort under the guidance of Eileen Cook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/projects/editing-portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 08:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/projects/editing-portfolio/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m on hiatus from editing projects while I head back to school to complete my degree. Thanks for understanding 💜 I offer manuscript consultations for the exploring author and in-depth editing services for authors with specific goals for their manuscript. That means everything from developmental editing and copy editing down to the nitty gritty of a proofread.
I enjoy a variety of speculative fiction genres, including fantasy, science-fiction, dystopian, gothic, and contemporary, and I like everything from middle grade up to and including adult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Writing</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/projects/other-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/projects/other-work/</guid>
      <description>Reedsy Short Story Contest Shortlisted
 The Assembly Line (science fiction, horror) The Devil’s in the Details (fantasy, humour) Five Golden Rings (contemporary, romance)  Other Submissions
 The Pipe Mage (fantasy, young adult) The Secret Ingredient (fantasy, young adult) Wind Whisperer (fantasy, young adult) Capuccino Cups (contemporary, psychological) Pulling the Plug (contemporary, humour) A Decade on a Train (contemporary, romance)  Non-Fiction Publications  The Guest House, The Lyre 2021 (lyrical essay, grief) “Weaving a Fantasy: Worldbuilding with Elise Volkman,” Let’s Talk Craft, Wattpad interview with Jess Wesley Living in a digital world: Tech tools break storytelling mould, WordWorks 2022 Volume II article 5 Years in the Business of Words, The Block Party (business anniversary post) How to Lure a Hermit to a Party: What the Heck is a Newsletter?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Nymph Keepers Trilogy</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/projects/the-nymph-keepers-trilogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 08:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/projects/the-nymph-keepers-trilogy/</guid>
      <description>Nym is the last living nymph in the province of Galia, and Jay is out for her blood.
      I write fantasy and science fiction and have a flair for gothic drama. The Nymph Keepers trilogy is my debut ebook series about Forest, a nymph whose people have been hunted to near-extinction for the healing properties in their blood. Jay needs nymph blood to help his sister, and Forest is supposed to be his solution to everything.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
