<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>book reviews on Elise Volkman</title>
    <link>https://elisevolkman.com/tags/book-reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in book reviews on Elise Volkman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 08:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://elisevolkman.com/tags/book-reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Spines Ya Crackin&#39;? 📚 (BOOK spines, that is)</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/what-spines-ya-crackin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/what-spines-ya-crackin/</guid>
      <description>Book spines! I swear I meant BOOK spines! I get that I&amp;rsquo;m a fantasy author with a penchant for the darker tales (though you cannot accuse me of publishing any tragedies, those will never see beyond the deep, dark reaches of a digital filing cabinet). But come ON.
It&amp;rsquo;s now 2024. The last time I updated anyone on my reading progress was last year, when I had read 26 books in the first quarter of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Soft Magic Systems Are So Hard to Write 🪄</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/hard-and-soft-magic-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/hard-and-soft-magic-systems/</guid>
      <description>It took me two attempts to finish reading For the Throne by Hannah Whitten. At first, I thought I was just bored because the book started off with different POV characters. But in the end, the thing that was really bothering me was the magic system.
Soft and hard magic systems are like the difference between Star Wars and Project Hail Mary. Everyone&amp;rsquo;s favourite space opera is pretty approachable even if you don&amp;rsquo;t care a lick about science, while Project Hail Mary, from the author of The Martian, will only appeal to those who are willing to learn about the nitty gritty details of the science at play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet My New Favourite Author, Plus a Few More 📚</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/meet-my-new-favourite-author-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/meet-my-new-favourite-author-2023/</guid>
      <description>Crows, security robots, seas made of spores, and a subspecies of dragon called a quigutl. Yes, dear friends. You&amp;rsquo;re in for a whole lot of good this quarter. If you need any reading material, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep you going for a while. My goal was to read 24 books by the end of this year — that&amp;rsquo;s one each month, in case you hate math as much as I do. Reason being, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t feeling like reading much at all for a while and didn&amp;rsquo;t think I could manage much more than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few More Good Reads: Happy New Year! 🥂</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/happy-new-year-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:30:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/happy-new-year-2022/</guid>
      <description>As I sat down to pick out my top reads of the last quarter of 2022, I looked at my list and thought to myself, &amp;ldquo;Well, this looks a lot more like me.&amp;rdquo; And yet, as I write this, I feel less like myself than I ever have. Aren&amp;rsquo;t people funny paradoxes? Funny isn&amp;rsquo;t the right word, but we use it like that all the time. Funny can mean can mean odd, unsettling, and uncomfortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Round-Up — September 2022</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/reading-round-up-september-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/reading-round-up-september-2022/</guid>
      <description>Skip to the books
Slowing Down But Never Stopping In August, I popped in here to talk about &amp;ldquo;good writing.&amp;rdquo; By that, I meant the three books I had read that year that made me say &amp;ldquo;I want to write like that one day.&amp;rdquo; (That&amp;rsquo;s the author&amp;rsquo;s version of &amp;ldquo;I want to be like them when I grow up.&amp;quot;) Since then, I have read eight books. Is that a lot? Eight books in two months?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Writing: My Top 3 Reads of 2022 (So Far)</title>
      <link>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/good-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 12:33:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elisevolkman.com/posts/good-writing/</guid>
      <description>An Enchantment of Ravens
If We Were Villains
The Love Hypothesis
To Read or Not To Read I can count on one hand the number of books I&amp;rsquo;ve read this year that have made me want to write. And I&amp;rsquo;ve read 30 books so far. Maybe those aren&amp;rsquo;t great odds. Maybe I should be more selective about the books I pick up; maybe I should DNF (did-not-finish) more often. But once I start reading something, I have an excruciatingly hard time stopping until I reach &amp;ldquo;The End.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
